what I'm gonna get it out before
research rolling it just means you're
getting comfortable with us I am I'm
comfortable you showing us all your
growth I can say that you guys can't say
that I don't know I just said it Chris
you can say that to me I feel like they
can see it yeah they can't say it you
can say yeah I don't want to say off
camera I'm gonna say it all on camera
doing on camera this is everyday this is
a talk show where we talk about what the
Internet's talking about the story today
Drake he's a rapper he released a new
single today in a music video for I'm
upset this comes weeks after beef with
the other rapper Pusha T just before we
started Jordan and Chris I heard you
guys talking about this I don't really
understand what's going on can you
[Laughter]
for years
Pusha T has not liked Drake I think he
thinks Drake is like fake and an
opportunist and he's like not black or
something like that
no she's black he just doesn't like the
way he portrays black in what way is
that he just drank this weird do man
he's very very like everything sucks I'm
at the time you beneath me it's very
weird but she makes me makes catchy
music I'm not gonna say I'm not I'm not
a drag big fan I don't hate them I don't
love them put your tears okay you know I
mean who do you say anymore it's not
really a more or less thing I'm gonna
take it from the aspect that push your
tea is winning right now I'll say that
is winning Izzy because the other guy is
way more successful and has a lot more
money and I'm talking about success and
money which all my success in linear and
what is winning so take me through the
poetry bash poem for poem put your tea
is with it so by the poetry bass rules
that were okay the video set the video
was good
the song is average at best but the
video is decent I might Degrassi fan and
I was like I need to know more about
this Degrassi I go to school no because
I was like that was my high school
experience so it's a very good kid in
high school so that was how I rebelled I
would watch it and was it or like it was
there was sex
you're gonna start a list there really
excited no but there's all the drama
that you need in a high school in one
episode it was great sex alcohol and
it's all it all takes place in Canada
yes it do you think is that why Drake is
weird to us because he's Canadian we
just don't understand his Canadian way
these people serve okay I think what
Nate is saying is do we not understand
drink because he's from this foreign
land that maybe we can't even point out
on a map it's called Canada
Natasha understand yeah I get what
you're saying thank you what no I think
we can I think we understand him just
fine I'm just gonna I was gonna say one
thing and I was gonna do you know what I
think we all get it well watch back the
tape earlier Chris said that Drake was
weird and we didn't understand him
because he was Canadian I think he said
all that so I'm just repeating what
Chris said really
wait you know what just happened we have
beef now we do I now have a public feud
with all of you because you you
embarrassed me publicly and now I'm
gonna come at you all hard
you little okay so Jordan you
haven't spoken in a while do you want to
say something
I think beefs are just like awkward
media opportunities to like advertise
for like when you're about to drop an
album which I think Drake is about to do
is that right yeah Chris yes I will say
even though it seems like the song is
about right like I'm mad the video I
found so inspirational did you watch it
to the end there was a shooting at the
end that was some sort of pyrotechnics
the high school went up in flames which
i think is symbolic of we are now moving
past our high school cells adults and it
should burn like our memories and
Natasha doubled down on the V video
being inspiring let us know what you
think in the comments we're going to do
something different right now hi I'm
Hannah Dickinson and this is cheers to
you where I'm kicking off my first round
of the weekend by choosing every person
and story that encourages me to drink
first off cheers to you ariana grande
for getting engaged to Pete Davidson
proving no matter how short a woman is
she will always date down and cheers to
you Pete Davidson we're spending ninety
three thousand dollars on a ring that's
commitment the most expensive gift of
guys ever given me is HPV and cheers to
you GOP congressman for getting back
into baseball practice now you can
finally take a swing at something other
than my reproductive rights cheers see
you physicists for concluding we aren't
living in a computer simulation I'm glad
you finally realize it's only real woman
who won't go cheers to you Jada
pinkett-smith for being so open about
masturbation it's good to know all the
Smiths are getting jiggy with it
yeah that joke is Wicky Wicky wild still
bad alright cheers to you I hop from
flipping your name to i hob I for one
won't be getting what I always do when I
drunkenly go there diarrhea okay cheers
to you BER for developing artificial
intelligence to detect drunk passengers
it's a long way to go to find white
girls and tube tops yelling Greg well
that's all the Martina and I have so
cheers to you and may your weekend be
filled with drama and regret so I can
start drinking next week this is
learning and burn in a segment where I
eat something really hot and then I
learned something and joining me as
always is real-life doctor of sociology
Nate Durand PhD that's Jeff that's true
is what I'm doing with today's burn is
habanero pepper and today's learn is
gender is a spectrum that works in just
a moment Ryan I'm gonna have you eat one
of these peppers you will then be
required to read a statement on this
card then I will ask you a series of
questions and only once you have
answered them all correctly we will be
given this week relief of a glass of
milk on milk duty today as always is
Chris cotton give it up for Chris cotton
everybody
is a special milk boy and we love Jesus
Christ I don't know that means okay
right
take the habanero pepper the orange one
the one of the orange ones in the center
I'm gonna I'm not gonna make a face
that's the goal and I'm gonna eat the
whole thing because I don't want any
only in the Internet to the internet to
make fun of me when you're ready
go pepper is in his mouth oh so bad
there's a distinction between a person's
biological sex and agender biological
sex is compromised of the reproductive
organs penis and vagina as well as
secondary sex characteristics I eat for
females and large presses this is so
long widen hips for males facial hair in
Adam's apple gender in contrast can
refer to either social rules imposed on
the sexes of a person by society ie
gender role versus personal
identification of one's own gender based
on an internal awareness ie gender
identity Nate begins questions from card
Ryan first question initial thoughts
we're gonna follow it correct next
question in a way that grandpa would
understand oh the difference between sex
and gender what in a way that a grandpa
would understand what's the difference
between sex and gender such as your
parts genders how you feel very good how
old were you when you follow up how was
that for you I was probably too old and
it was like too old it was awkward I'm
gonna accept that Ryan the academic
Judas mother argue the gender is
performative rather than a biological
fact agree or disagree Ryan you're
talking too fast gender is performative
yeah correct Ryan if men are so strong
then why is masculinity so fragile we
need more than that Ryan I'm gonna need
more than that uh-huh
your eyes are watering right are you
demonstrating you can cry you're allowed
to cry that doesn't mean you're not a
man right we have a masculinity problem
in America and I don't know exactly how
to sum it up in this segment that's
right last question on the card that I
just had you read you listed for
secondary sex characteristics what were
they that's your mouth
boobs that's right enlarged breasts for
women
what last one what's the secondary sex
characteristic for women you're getting
some help from the gallery penis hips
this was not a large dicks is correct
given the milk that was learning and
burning please leave a comment what you
would like us to learn
[Laughter]
that's the episode we'll see you
tomorrow never done this Wow
[Applause]
[Music]
you